Help on class DynamicFetcher in module scrapling.fetchers.chrome:

class DynamicFetcher(scrapling.engines.toolbelt.custom.BaseFetcher)
 |  DynamicFetcher(*args, **kwargs)
 |
 |  A `Fetcher` that provide many options to fetch/load websites' pages through chromium-based browsers.
 |
 |  Method resolution order:
 |      DynamicFetcher
 |      scrapling.engines.toolbelt.custom.BaseFetcher
 |      builtins.object
 |
 |  Class methods defined here:
 |
 |  async async_fetch(url: str, **kwargs: Unpack[PlaywrightSession]) -> Response
 |      Opens up a browser and do your request based on your chosen options below.
 |
 |      :param url: Target url.
 |      :param headless: Run the browser in headless/hidden (default), or headful/visible mode.
 |      :param disable_resources: Drop requests for unnecessary resources for a speed boost.
 |      :param blocked_domains: A set of domain names to block requests to. Subdomains are also matched (e.g., ``"example.com"`` blocks ``"sub.example.com"`` too).
 |      :param useragent: Pass a useragent string to be used. Otherwise the fetcher will generate a real Useragent of the same browser and use it.
 |      :param cookies: Set cookies for the next request.
 |      :param network_idle: Wait for the page until there are no network connections for at least 500 ms.
 |      :param load_dom: Enabled by default, wait for all JavaScript on page(s) to fully load and execute.
 |      :param timeout: The timeout in milliseconds that is used in all operations and waits through the page. The default is 30,000
 |      :param wait: The time (milliseconds) the fetcher will wait after everything finishes before closing the page and returning the Response object.
 |      :param page_action: Added for automation. A function that takes the `page` object and does the automation you need.
 |      :param wait_selector: Wait for a specific CSS selector to be in a specific state.
 |      :param init_script: An absolute path to a JavaScript file to be executed on page creation with this request.
 |      :param locale: Set the locale for the browser if wanted. Defaults to the system default locale.
 |      :param wait_selector_state: The state to wait for the selector given with `wait_selector`. The default state is `attached`.
 |      :param real_chrome: If you have a Chrome browser installed on your device, enable this, and the Fetcher will launch an instance of your browser and use it.
 |      :param cdp_url: Instead of launching a new browser instance, connect to this CDP URL to control real browsers through CDP.
 |      :param google_search: Enabled by default, Scrapling will set a Google referer header.
 |      :param extra_headers: A dictionary of extra headers to add to the request.
 |      :param proxy: The proxy to be used with requests, it can be a string or a dictionary with the keys 'server', 'username', and 'password' only.
 |      :param extra_flags: A list of additional browser flags to pass to the browser on launch.
 |      :param selector_config: The arguments that will be passed in the end while creating the final Selector's class.
 |      :param additional_args: Additional arguments to be passed to Playwright's context as additional settings.
 |      :return: A `Response` object.
 |
 |  fetch(url: str, **kwargs: Unpack[PlaywrightSession]) -> Response
 |      Opens up a browser and do your request based on your chosen options below.
 |
 |      :param url: Target url.
 |      :param headless: Run the browser in headless/hidden (default), or headful/visible mode.
 |      :param disable_resources: Drop requests for unnecessary resources for a speed boost.
 |      :param blocked_domains: A set of domain names to block requests to. Subdomains are also matched (e.g., ``"example.com"`` blocks ``"sub.example.com"`` too).
 |      :param useragent: Pass a useragent string to be used. Otherwise the fetcher will generate a real Useragent of the same browser and use it.
 |      :param cookies: Set cookies for the next request.
 |      :param network_idle: Wait for the page until there are no network connections for at least 500 ms.
 |      :param load_dom: Enabled by default, wait for all JavaScript on page(s) to fully load and execute.
 |      :param timeout: The timeout in milliseconds that is used in all operations and waits through the page. The default is 30,000
 |      :param wait: The time (milliseconds) the fetcher will wait after everything finishes before closing the page and returning the Response object.
 |      :param page_action: Added for automation. A function that takes the `page` object and does the automation you need.
 |      :param wait_selector: Wait for a specific CSS selector to be in a specific state.
 |      :param init_script: An absolute path to a JavaScript file to be executed on page creation with this request.
 |      :param locale: Set the locale for the browser if wanted. Defaults to the system default locale.
 |      :param wait_selector_state: The state to wait for the selector given with `wait_selector`. The default state is `attached`.
 |      :param real_chrome: If you have a Chrome browser installed on your device, enable this, and the Fetcher will launch an instance of your browser and use it.
 |      :param cdp_url: Instead of launching a new browser instance, connect to this CDP URL to control real browsers through CDP.
 |      :param google_search: Enabled by default, Scrapling will set a Google referer header.
 |      :param extra_headers: A dictionary of extra headers to add to the request.
 |      :param proxy: The proxy to be used with requests, it can be a string or a dictionary with the keys 'server', 'username', and 'password' only.
 |      :param extra_flags: A list of additional browser flags to pass to the browser on launch.
 |      :param selector_config: The arguments that will be passed in the end while creating the final Selector's class.
 |      :param additional_args: Additional arguments to be passed to Playwright's context as additional settings.
 |      :return: A `Response` object.
 |
 |  ----------------------------------------------------------------------
 |  Data descriptors defined here:
 |
 |  __dict__
 |      dictionary for instance variables
 |
 |  __weakref__
 |      list of weak references to the object
 |
 |  ----------------------------------------------------------------------
 |  Methods inherited from scrapling.engines.toolbelt.custom.BaseFetcher:
 |
 |  __init__(self, *args, **kwargs)
 |      Initialize self.  See help(type(self)) for accurate signature.
 |
 |  storage = SQLiteStorageSystem(storage_file: str, url: Optional[str] = None)
 |      The recommended system to use, it's race condition safe and thread safe.
 |      Mainly built, so the library can run in threaded frameworks like scrapy or threaded tools
 |      > It's optimized for threaded applications, but running it without threads shouldn't make it slow.
 |
 |  ----------------------------------------------------------------------
 |  Class methods inherited from scrapling.engines.toolbelt.custom.BaseFetcher:
 |
 |  configure(**kwargs)
 |      Set multiple arguments for the parser at once globally
 |
 |      :param kwargs: The keywords can be any arguments of the following: huge_tree, keep_comments, keep_cdata, adaptive, storage, storage_args, adaptive_domain
 |
 |  display_config()
 |
 |  ----------------------------------------------------------------------
 |  Data and other attributes inherited from scrapling.engines.toolbelt.custom.BaseFetcher:
 |
 |  adaptive = False
 |
 |  adaptive_domain = ''
 |
 |  huge_tree = True
 |
 |  keep_cdata = False
 |
 |  keep_comments = False
 |
 |  parser_keywords = ('huge_tree', 'adaptive', 'storage', 'keep_cdata', '...
 |
 |  storage_args = None

